Register of the Allen Drury papers 65007.4088171
Hoover Institution Archives
Allen Drury papers
1890-1995
Hoover Institution Archives
Drury, Allen.
65007.4088171
29.5 linear feet 75 manuscript boxes, 1 card file box, 7 envelopes, 6 phonorecords, 18 phonotape cassettes, 2 videotape cassettes
Correspondence, drafts of writings, galley proofs, book reviews, memorabilia, sound recordings, and photographs, relating to the novelistic treatment of twentieth-century American politics by news correspondent and Pulitzer Prize-winning author Allen Drury.
Cassette cabinet
Photo file
Tape cabinet Beta, U-Matic, 1/2" tapes
Box 1
Oversize photo file
Box 1-62
Shelf 12.08/09
Record cabinet
Box 66-67
Shelf 107.05
Box 63-65
Shelf 124.02
Box 75
Shelf 16.43
Tape cabinet VHS
Box 13
Box 68-74
Shelf 31.10.
Access
The collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least two business days in advance of intended use.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1963, with increments added until Drury's death in 1998.
Chronology
1918 September 2 Born, Houston, Texas
1939 B.A., Stanford University
1940-1941 Editor, Tulare Bee, awarded national Sigma Delta Chi Editorial Award for writings in this publication
1941-1943 Editor, The Bakersfield Californian
1942-1943 Served in the United States Army
1943-1946 United States Senate staff of United Press
1954-1959 Washington reporter, New York Times
1959 Author, Advise and Consent
1960 Awarded Pulitzer Prize
1961 Author, Education for Politics
1962 Author, A Shade of Difference
1963 Author, A Senate Journal, 1943-1945
1965 Author, That Summer
1966 Author, Capable of Honor
1967 Author, A Very Strange Society
1968 Author, Preserve and Protect
1971 Author, Courage and Hesitation, Author, The Throne of Saturn
1973 Author, Come Nineveh, Come Tyre
1975 Author, The Promise of Joy
1976 Author, A God Against the Gods
1980 Author, Egypt: The Eternal Smile
1981 Author, The Hill of Summer
1982 Appointed to the National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities
1983 Author, Decision
1984 Author, The Roads of Earth
1986 Author, Pentagon
1990 Author, Toward What Bright Glory?
1993 Author, Into What Far Harbor?
1995 Author, A Thing of State
1998 Author, Public Men
1998 September 2 Died, Marin County, California
1918 September 2 Born, Houston, Texas
1939 B.A., Stanford University
1940-1941 Editor, Tulare Bee, awarded national Sigma Delta Chi Editorial Award for writings in this publication
1941-1943 Editor, The Bakersfield Californian
1942-1943 Served in the United States Army
1943-1946 United States Senate staff of United Press
1954-1959 Washington reporter, New York Times
1959 Author, Advise and Consent
1960 Awarded Pulitzer Prize
1961 Author, Education for Politics
1962 Author, A Shade of Difference
1963 Author, A Senate Journal, 1943-1945
1965 Author, That Summer
1966 Author, Capable of Honor
1967 Author, A Very Strange Society
1968 Author, Preserve and Protect
1971 Author, Courage and Hesitation, Author, The Throne of Saturn
1973 Author, Come Nineveh, Come Tyre
1975 Author, The Promise of Joy
1976 Author, A God Against the Gods
1980 Author, Egypt: The Eternal Smile
1981 Author, The Hill of Summer
1982 Appointed to the National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities
1983 Author, Decision
1984 Author, The Roads of Earth
1986 Author, Pentagon
1990 Author, Toward What Bright Glory?
1993 Author, Into What Far Harbor?
1995 Author, A Thing of State
1998 Author, Public Men
1998 September 2 Died, Marin County, California
Scope and Content of Collection
The first part of the papers of Allen Drury was acquired by the Hoover Institution in 1963. Increments continued to be added until his death in 1998. The papers relate to Allen Drury's career as news correspondent turned Pulitzer Prize-winning author.
The bulk of the papers are the speeches and writing series, which spans the years 1932 through 1995. Included in this series are drafts and galley proofs for his books, as well as numerous articles which were published separately. Most of his writings pertain to the subjects of American politics and foreign relations.
Of significance is Drury's extensive correspondence with a wide array of politicians, heads of state, and celebrities. Included are letters to and from Presidents Lyndon Johnson, Richard Nixon, and Ronald Reagan.
Drury's professional and social contacts illustrated by material in the biographical series, tie in closely to his work as author and journalist.
Arrangement
Arranged into eight series: Bigraphical File, Correspondence File, Speeches and Writings, Memorabilia, Card Index, Photographs, Sound Recordings, and Videorecordings.
Audiotapes.; Phonorecords.; United States--Politics and government--1945-1989--Fiction.; Video tapes.; Drury, Allen.
- Biographical File, 1931-1989
  Scope and Contents note
  Appointment calendar, certificates, clippings, drawings, identification badges, passports, yearbooks and other material relating to the career and life of Allen Drury, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - General
    - General, 1931-1966 (Folder 1: 1)
    - "An Exclusive Interview with Allen Drury," Writer's Yearbook, 1968. (Folder 1: 2)
      Printed copy
    - Collected materials from press assignments
      - Democratic and Republican Party conventions (Folder 1: 3)
        - 1948 (Folder 1: 4)
        - 1948-1960 (Folder 1: 5)
      - National Founding Convention of the New Party, Philadelphia, 1948 July 23-25 (Folder 1: 6)
      - Truman, Harry S., trips
        - West coast, 1950 May 7-16 (Folder 1: 7)
        - Connecticut, Massachusetts, Rhode Island and Brooklyn, 1952 October 15-19 (Folder 1: 8)
    - Military status, 1942 (Folder 1: 9)
    - Trips
      - 1960-1975 (Folder 2: 1)
      - 1976-1977 (Folder 2: 2)
    - Appointment calendar, 1965 (Folder 2: 3)
    - Certificates, commendations, diplomas, 1935-1988 (Folder 2: 4)
    - Clippings relating to the career and life of Allen Drury
      - 1941-1946 (Folder 2: 5)
      - 1950-1962 (Folder 2: 6)
      - 1959-1962 (Folder 2: 7)
      - 1963-1965 (Folder 2: 8)
      - 1966-1972 (Box-folder 3: 1)
      - 1972-1975 (Folder 3: 2)
      - 1979-1980 (Folder 3: 3)
      - 1981-1989 (Folder 3: 4)
    - Curriculum vitae, 1966-1988 (Folder 3: 5)
    - Drawings by Allen Drury, undated (Folder 3: 6)
    - Identification and membership cards
      - 1951-1973 (Folder 3: 7)
      - 1951-1976 (Folder 3: 8)
    - Invitations
      - 1946-1956 (Folder 4: 1)
      - 1952-1969 (Folder 4: 2)
      - 1964-1969 (Folder 4: 3)
      - 1964-1977 (Folder 4: 4)
      - 1985-1986 (Folder 4: 5)
    - Mailing receipts, 1965 (Folder 4: 6)
    - Passports, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 5: 1)
    - War ration book, 1943 October (Folder 5: 2)
    - Yearbooks, Porterville Union High School (California)
      - 1932-1934 (Folder 5: 3)
      - 1935 (Folder 5: 4)
- Correspondence File, 1890-1994.
  Letters sent and received by Allen Drury, arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent
  - General
    - General
      - 1945-1965 (Folder 5: 5)
      - 1966-1971 (Folder 5: 6)
      - 1971-1973 (Folder 5: 7)
      - 1973-1975 (Box-folder 6: 1)
      - 1976-1980 (Folder 6: 2)
      - 1981-1984 (Folder 6: 3)
      - 1984-1985 (Folder 6: 4)
      - 1985-1986 (Folder 6: 5)
      - 1987 (Folder 6: 6)
      - 1987-1988 (Box-folder 7: 1)
      - 1988-1990 (Folder 7: 2)
      - 1991-1994 (Folder 7: 3)
    - Campaign of William F. Knowland, 1946 (Folder 7: 4)
    - Charities, donations, 1970-1972 (Folder 7: 5)
    - Clubs and memberships, 1964-1971 (Folder 7: 6)
    - Colleges and universities, 1962-1966 (Folder 7: 7)
    - Family
      - General, 1890-1986 (Folder 7: 8)
      - Drury, Alden and Flora
        - 1942-1945 (Folder 7: 9)
        - 1945-1946 (Box-folder 8: 1)
        - 1948-1973 (Folder 8: 2)
      - Drury, Doris, 1963 (Folder 8: 3)
      - Drury, Hope, undated (Folder 8: 4)
      - Drury, Marian, 1943-1963 (Folder 8: 5)
      - Killiany, Ann Drury, 1942-1973 (Folder 8 :6)
      - Killiany, Kenneth, 1982-1983 (Folder 8: 7)
        (closed until August 2015)
      - Killiany, Kevin, 1973 (Folder 8: 8)
    - Fans
      - 1956-1959 (Folder 8: 9)
      - 1959-1961 (Folder 8: 10)
      - 1961-1963 (Box-folder 9: 1)
      - 1962-1966 (Folder 9: 2)
      - 1964-1967 (Folder 9: 3)
      - 1967-1968 (Folder 9: 4)
      - 1968 (Folder 9: 5)
      - 1969 (Box-folder 10: 1)
      - 1969-1970 (Folder 10: 2)
      - 1960-1972 (Folder 10: 3)
      - 1971-1972 (Folder 10: 4)
      - 1972-1973 (Folder 10: 5)
      - 1974 (Folder 10: 6)
      - 1974-1978 (Box-folder 11: 1)
      - 1974-1975 (Folder 11: 2)
      - 1978-1979 (Folder 11: 3)
      - 1980-1986 (Folder 11: 4)
    - Financial matters
      - 1959-1973 (Folder 11: 5)
      - 1960-1986 (Folder 11: 6)
    - Friends and colleagues of Richard M. Nixon, 1971-1972 (Folder 11: 7)
    - Publishers, 1960-1986 (Box-folder 12: 1)
    - Real estate property, 1971-1973 (Folder 12: 2)
    - Sanibel-Captiva Islands development, 1970 (Folder 12: 3)
    - South Africa
      - 1965-1966 (Folder 12: 4)
      - 1967-1976 (Folder 12: 5)
      - 1981-1989 (Folder 12: 6)
    - Speaking engagements
      - 1953-1967 (Folder 12: 7)
      - 1968-1974 (Box-folder 13: 1)
      - 1982-1987 (Folder 13: 2)
    - Taiwan, 1981-1988 (Folder 13: 3)
  - Abenheim, Donald, 1989 (Folder 13: 4)
  - Adams, Barry L., 1970 (Folder 13: 5)
  - Adler, Kurt H., 1984 (Folder 13: 6)
  - Agnew, Spiro, 1969-1971 (Folder 13: 7)
  - Aiken, George D., 1960-1974 (Folder 13: 8)
  - Aldred, Cyril, 1974-1976 (Folder 13: 9)
  - Allen, Fred D. ( Tulare Bee), 1959 (Folder 13: 10)
  - Allen, Marty, 1973 (Folder 13: 11)
  - American Academy of Achievement, 1967-1970 (Folder 13: 12)
  - American Association for the United Nations, Capitol Area Division, 1962-1963 (Folder 13: 13)
  - Anderson, Anna H., undated (Folder 13: 14)
  - Anderson, Martin, 1990-1992 (Folder 13: 15)
  - Anthony Productions, Inc., 1977 (Folder 13: 16)
  - Arce, Phil, undated (Folder 13: 17)
  - Ardrey, Robert, 1963-1970 (Folder 13: 18)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1963-1969 (Folder 13: 19)
  - Associated Press, 1961 (Folder 13: 20)
  - Atheneum Publishers, 1966-1973 (Folder 13: 21)
  - Atlantic Monthly, 1941 (Folder 13: 22)
  - Author's Guild, 1965-1971 (Folder 13: 23)
  - Author's League Fund, 1970 (Folder 13: 24)
  - Bacchus, James, 1972 (Folder 13: 25)
  - Baker, George, 1966-1973 (Folder 13: 26)
  - Baker, Howard H., 1979 (Folder 13: 27)
  - Baker, Leonard, 1966 (Folder 13: 28)
  - Barber, Carter, 1963 (Folder 13: 29)
  - Barbour, Janet, 1971 (Folder 13: 30)
  - Barbour, Tom, 1971 (Folder 13: 31)
  - Barkham, John, 1968 (Folder 13: 32)
  - Barr, Bob, 1969-1971 (Folder 13: 33)
  - Barrett, Karen, 1971 (Folder 13: 34)
  - Batman, L. R., 1959 (Folder 13: 35)
  - Beale, Betty, 1973 (Folder 13: 36)
  - Beecher, Ward, 1959 (Folder 13: 37)
  - Bender Warehouse Company, 1969 (Folder 13: 38)
  - Bennett, Charles E., 1961-1973 (Folder 13: 39)
  - Benson, Ezra Taft, 1967 (Folder 13: 40)
  - Bentley, Elizabeth, undated (Folder 13: 41)
  - Bentley, Wilmer, 1971 (Folder 13: 42)
  - Bentsen, Lloyd, 1973 (Folder 13: 43)
  - Berg and Faircloth, 1967-1970 (Folder 13: 44)
  - Berger, Lynne, 1968 (Folder 13: 45)
  - Bergeron, Victor, 1976 (Folder 13: 46)
  - Best Selling Books for the Blind, 1971 (Folder 13: 47)
  - Bishop, Alvin H., 1969 (Folder 13: 48)
  - Black, Shirley Temple, 1990 (Folder 13: 49)
  - Boatner, Charles, 1969 (Folder 13: 50)
  - Boddy, B. W., 1973 (Folder 13: 51)
  - Boggs, Hale, 1963-1966 (Folder 13: 52)
  - Boggs, J. Caleb, 1963 (Folder 13: 53)
  - Bohemian Club, 1966-1993 (Folder 13: 54)
  - Boisson, R., 1960 (Folder 13: 55)
  - Bombeck, Erma, 1983 (Folder 13: 56)
  - Booth, Jean, 1973 (Folder 13: 57)
  - Bradbury, Ray, 1971 (Folder 13: 58)
  - Bradley, Jim, 1960 (Folder 13: 59)
  - Brady, James W., 1970 (Folder 13: 60)
  - Brandstetter, Frank M., 1976 (Folder 13: 61)
  - Brewer, Albert P., 1968 (Folder 13: 62)
  - Brinkley, Mrs. David, undated (Folder 13: 63)
  - Brinkley, Don, 1978 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - British-American Parliamentary Group, 1960 (Folder 14: 2)
  - Brooke, Edward W., 1973-1974 (Folder 14: 3)
  - Brown, E. L., 1972 (Folder 14: 4)
  - Buckley, James, 1973 (Folder 14: 5)
  - Buckley, Sean and Joan, 1972 (Folder 14: 6)
  - Buckley, William F., 1968-1975 (Folder 14: 7)
  - Bunche, Ralph, 1968 (Folder 14: 8)
  - Bush, George, 1971-1988 (Folder 14: 9)
  - Byrd, Harry. F., 1959-1987 (Folder 14: 10)
  - Cail, Mary, undated (Folder 14: 11)
  - Calfee, David W., 1960 (Folder 14: 12)
  - California Newspaper Publishers Association, 1942 (Folder 14: 13)
  - Californian, 1941 (Folder 14: 14)
  - Capozzoli, Louis, 1962 (Folder 14: 15)
  - Carlin, William J., 1969 (Folder 14: 16)
  - Carney, James H., 1972 (Folder 14: 17)
  - Carpenter, Elizabeth, 1965-1974 (Folder 14: 18)
  - Carpenter, Leslie, 1962 (Folder 14: 19)
  - Carr, Lawrence, 1960 (Folder 14: 20)
  - Carter, John Mack, 1968 (Folder 14: 21)
  - CBS News, 1959 (Folder 14: 22)
  - Cernan, Barbara and Gene, 1971 (Folder 14: 23)
  - Channing, Carol, 1972-1974 (Folder 14: 24)
  - Chapman, Hester, 1972-1973 (Folder 14: 25)
  - Church, Frank, 1963-1965 (Folder 14: 26)
  - Citizens for Goldwater-Miller, 1964 (Folder 14: 27)
  - Clark, Deena, 1963-1972 (Folder 14: 28)
  - Clark, William P., 1982-1984 (Folder 14: 29)
  - Coffin, Tris, 1959 (Folder 14: 30)
  - Cogswell, Elinor, undated (Folder 14: 31)
  - Cohn, Joseph, 1973-1975 (Folder 14: 32)
  - Collins Publishers, 1959-1962 (Folder 14: 33)
  - Colson, Charles W., 1971 (Folder 14: 34)
  - Commonwealth Club of California, 1984-1990 (Folder 14: 35)
  - Conomos, William G., 1968-1970 (Folder 14: 36)
  - Cook, Liz, undated (Folder 14: 37)
  - Cooper, John Sherman, 1959-1963 (Folder 14: 38)
  - Coppel, Alfred, 1971 (Folder 14: 39)
  - Corbett, Jack, 1970 (Folder 14: 40)
  - Corker, Alma, 1960 (Folder 14: 41)
  - Cotton, Aylett, 1967-1968 (Folder 14: 42)
  - Cousins, Norman, 1966 (Folder 14: 43)
  - Coward-McCann, Incorporated, 1964-1967 (Folder 14: 44)
  - Craig, May, 1962 (Folder 14: 45)
  - Cranston, Alan, 1973 (Folder 14: 46)
  - Crawford, Joan, 1963-1975 (Folder 14: 47)
  - Crockett, Jim, 1953 (Folder 14: 48)
  - Cronkite, Walter, 1959 (Folder 14: 49)
  - Culver, Rosalie, 1972 (Folder 14: 50)
  - Curtis Publishing Company, 1965 (Folder 14: 51)
  - Daily Telegraph and Morning Post (London), 1971 (Folder 14: 52)
  - Daniel, Clifton, 1960 (Folder 14: 53)
  - David, Harry, 1960 (Folder 14: 54)
  - De La Salle High School, undated (Folder 14: 55)
  - Des Moines Register and Tribune, undated (Folder 14: 56)
  - De Wyman, Herma, 1970 (Folder 14: 57)
  - Diaz Ordaz, Gustavo, 1964 (Folder 14: 58)
  - Dibble, Allen, 1959 (Folder 14: 59)
  - Dillon, Richard, 1967 (Folder 14: 60)
  - Dodd, Thomas J., 1959-1961 (Folder 14: 61)
  - Doubleday and Company
    - 1959-1969 (Folder 14: 62-63)
    - 1966-1968 (Box-folder 15: 1)
    - 1970-1971 (Folder 15: 2)
    - 1971-1973 (Folder 15: 3)
    - 1973-1974 (Folder 15: 4)
    - 1974-1981 (Folder 15: 5)
    - 1983-1988 (Folder 15: 6)
  - Douglas, Paul H., 1959-1966 (Folder 15: 7)
  - Douglass, Paul, 1971 (Folder 15: 8)
  - Drukill Company, 1960-1965 (Folder 15: 9)
  - Dunphy, Robert, 1963 (Folder 15: 10)
  - Eastern Montana College, 1968 (Folder 15: 11)
  - Edward, Willard, 1966 (Folder 15: 12)
  - Efron, Edith, undated (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Elbright, Carl, 1960 (Folder 16: 2)
  - Ellender, Allen, 1959 (Folder 16: 3)
  - Evening Telegraph of London, 1991 (Folder 16: 4)
  - Family Weekly (New York), 1964-1966 (Folder 16: 5)
  - Farley, James A., 1960 (Folder 16: 6)
  - Farr, Cyril, 1960 (Folder 16: 7)
  - Feinstein, Dianne, 1980-1984 (Folder 16: 8)
  - Feldstein, Joel, 1963 (Folder 16: 9)
  - Fielding, Fred, 1982 (Folder 16: 10)
  - Fielding, Nancy, 1971-1973 (Folder 16: 11)
  - Fielding, Temple, 1969-1976 (Folder 16: 12)
  - Fowler, Joseph, 1969 (Folder 16: 13)
  - Frankenhaler, Helen, 1988-1991 (Folder 16: 14)
  - Franklin Library (New York), 1982-1983 (Folder 16: 15)
  - Freeman, Lars, 1972 (Folder 16: 16)
  - Freidel, Frank, 1959-1966 (Folder 16: 17)
  - Frey, Louis, 1969-1972 (Folder 16: 18)
  - Fryer, Robert, 1969 (Folder 16: 19)
  - Fulbright, J. W., 1963-1973 (Folder 16: 20)
  - Gair, Floyd G., 1964 (Folder 16: 21)
  - Gerity, James, 1970 (Folder 16: 22)
  - Ghent, Henri, 1972-1973 (Folder 16: 23)
  - Gill, William J., 1970 (Folder 16: 24)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1966-1984 (Folder 16: 25)
  - Good Housekeeping, 1969 (Folder 16: 26)
  - Gore, Albert, 1963 (Folder 16: 27)
  - Gotfryd, Alex, 1985 (Folder 16: 28)
  - Greater Aspen Development Company, 1969 (Folder 16: 29)
  - Greater Orlando Press Club, 1970 (Folder 16: 30)
  - Griffin, Robert P., 1973 (Folder 16: 31)
  - Grimes, Tammy, undated (Folder 16: 32)
  - Gros, Robert R., 1963 (Folder 16: 33)
  - Gruening, Ernest, 1963 (Folder 16: 34)
  - Guerard, Albert, 1941 (Folder 16: 35)
  - Gundy, Edward and Helen, 1967-1968 (Folder 16: 36)
  - Gunter, Bill, 1973 (Folder 16: 37)
  - Hagerty, James C., 1967 (Folder 16: 38)
  - Haig, Alexander, 1971 (Folder 16: 39)
  - Haldeman, H. R., 1971 (Folder 16: 40)
  - Hall, Renee Renouf, 1965 (Folder 16: 41)
  - Halpern, Seymour, 1972 (Folder 16: 42)
  - Halsey, Lucia, undated (Folder 16: 43)
  - Halvorsen, David, 1984 (Folder 16: 44)
  - Hanna, Fred, 1972 (Folder 16: 45)
  - Hargrave, Colleen Moore, 1976-1977 (Folder 16: 46)
  - Harlow, Bryce, 1969 (Folder 16: 47)
  - Harold Matson Company
    - 1959-1968 (Folder 16: 48)
    - 1965-1968 (Folder 16: 49)
    - 1969 (Folder 16: 50)
    - 1970-1976 (Box-folder 17: 1)
    - 1976-1979 (Folder 17: 2)
    - 1981-1983 (Folder 17: 3)
  - Harper and Row, Publishers, 1966 (Folder 17: 4)
  - Harper's, 1973 (Folder 17: 5)
  - Harrison, Elizabeth, 1962 (Folder 17: 6)
  - Hart, Gary, 1979 (Folder 17: 7)
  - Harwood, Lee, 1959 (Folder 17: 8)
  - Hatch, Orrin, 1981-1993 (Folder 17: 9)
  - Hawkins, Paula, 1981-1983 (Folder 17: 10)
  - Hendershot, Mary F., 1965 (Folder 17: 11)
  - Herchenroether, Peter, 1970 (Folder 17: 12)
  - Herter, Christian A., 1960 (Folder 17: 13)
  - Higman, Howard, 1972 (Folder 17: 14)
  - Hill, Lister, 1963 (Folder 17: 15)
  - Hill, Milt Dean, 1960 (Folder 17: 16)
  - Hogan, William, 1976 (Folder 17: 17)
  - Holland, Isabelle, 1972 (Folder 17: 18)
  - Holloway, Marlon, 1971 (Folder 17: 19)
  - Hoover, Herbert C., 1941 (Folder 17: 20)
  - Hoover Institution, 1960-1991 (Folder 17: 21)
  - Houston, James, D., 1972 (Folder 17: 22)
  - Hruska, Roman, 1963 (Folder 17: 23)
  - Hughes, Lawrence, 1973 (Folder 17: 24)
  - Hughes, Riley, 1962 (Folder 17: 25)
  - Humphrey, Hubert, 1966-1973 (Folder 17: 26)
  - Huston, Luther, undated (Folder 17: 27)
  - IBM Corporation, 1963 (Folder 17: 28)
  - Inouye, Daniel, 1963 (Folder 17: 29)
  - Israel (Los Angeles), 1966 (Folder 17: 30)
  - Jackson, Henry M., 1968-1981 (Folder 17: 31)
  - Javits, Jacob K., 1962-1963 (Folder 17: 32)
  - Jernigan, Rupert L., 1966 (Folder 17: 33)
  - Johnson, Alice, 1960 (Folder 17: 34)
  - Johnson, Dana, 1973 (Folder 17: 35)
  - Johnson, Dorothy, 1968 (Folder 17: 36)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1974-1990 (Folder 17: 37)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1961-1968 (Folder 17: 38)
  - Jordan, Len, 1971 (Folder 17: 39)
  - Karrick, David B., 1959 (Folder 17: 40)
  - Keating, Kenneth, 1959-1961 (Folder 17: 41)
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1963 (Folder 17: 42)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1962 (Folder 17: 43)
  - Keogh, James, 1973 (Folder 17: 44)
  - Kerwin, Robert W., 1972 (Folder 17: 45)
  - Kieffer, Jean B., 1976 (Folder 17: 46)
  - Kiley, Richard, undated (Folder 17: 47)
  - Kimmit, J. S., 1969 (Folder 17: 48)
  - King Features Syndicate, 1941-1969 (Folder 17: 49)
  - Kiplinger Book Club, 1961 (Folder 17: 50)
  - Klein, Herbert G., 1971 (Folder 17: 51)
  - Kline, Herbert, 1970 (Folder 17: 52)
  - Kluckhohn, Frank L., 1969 (Folder 17: 53)
  - Knight, Allen, 1960 (Folder 17: 54)
  - Krock, Arthur, 1963-1969 (Folder 17: 55)
  - Kuchel, Thomas H., 1963 (Folder 17: 56)
  - Kuder, Frederic, 1972 (Folder 17: 57)
  - Kuhn, Edward, 1971 (Folder 17: 58)
  - Ladner, Millie, 1966-1972 (Folder 17: 59)
  - La Follette, Robert, 1946 (Folder 17: 60)
  - Laise, Carol C., 1973 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Lamborn, Robert L., 1973 (Folder 18: 2)
  - Lanchester, Elsa, 1968-1970 (Folder 18: 3)
  - Lantz, Robert, 1984 (Folder 18: 4)
  - Lantz Office, 1984-1985 (Folder 18: 5)
  - Larrabee, Don, 1973 (Folder 18: 6)
  - Learsy, Raymond J., 1984 (Folder 18: 7)
  - Le Baron, Robert, 1973 (Folder 18: 8)
  - Lefkoe Consulting, Incorporated, 1962-1970 (Folder 18: 9)
  - Leigh, W. Colston, 1962-1968 (Folder 18: 10)
  - Levy, Frank, R., 1977-1982 (Folder 18: 11)
  - Lewis, Hobart, 1962 (Folder 18: 12)
  - Library of Congress, 1970 (Folder 18: 13)
  - Look, 1971 (Folder 18: 14)
  - Luce, Clare B., 1974-1983 (Folder 18: 15)
  - Luce, Henry, III, 1988 (Folder 18: 16)
  - Mabon, Dickson, 1971 (Folder 18: 17)
  - MacInnes, Helen, 1973 (Folder 18: 18)
  - Madden, Betty, undated (Folder 18: 19)
  - Manchester Union Leader, 1964 (Folder 18: 20)
  - Mandel, Loring, 1960 (Folder 18: 21)
  - Mansfield, Mike, 1961-1981 (Folder 18: 22)
  - Marks, Milton, 1990 (Folder 18: 23)
  - Maroon, Fred J., 1972 (Folder 18: 24)
  - Marquand, John, 1959 (Folder 18: 25)
  - Mayes, Herbert, 1968-1976 (Folder 18: 26)
  - Mazanec, George L., 1969 (Folder 18: 27)
  - Mazo, Earl, 1971 (Folder 18: 28)
  - McCall Corporation, 1964-1968 (Folder 18: 29)
  - McCalls, 1959-1968 (Folder 18: 30)
  - McClellan, John L., 1970-1973 (Folder 18: 31)
  - McCormick, Anne, 1972 (Folder 18: 32)
  - McCormick, Ken, 1959-1967 (Folder 18: 33)
  - McGaffin, William, 1971 (Folder 18: 34)
  - McGee, Gale, 1963 (Folder 18: 35)
  - McGovern, George, 1979 (Folder 18: 36)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1963-1965 (Folder 18: 37)
  - McKee, Gladys, 1966 (Folder 18: 38)
  - McKelway, Benjamin, 1961 (Folder 18: 39)
  - McMillen, D. F., 1964 (Folder 18: 40)
  - Meier, Carla, 1973 (Folder 18: 41)
  - Mesta, Perle, 1972 (Folder 18: 42)
  - Michael Joseph Limited, 1962-1985 (Folder 18: 43)
  - Michener, James A., 1968 (Folder 18: 44)
  - Millis, Bill, 1942 (Folder 18: 45)
  - Milloy, James, 1959 (Folder 18: 46)
  - Mills Memorial Library, Rollins College (Winter Park, Florida), 1968 (Folder 18: 47)
  - Minneapolis Star and Tribune, 1953 (Folder 18: 48)
  - Mollenhoff, Clark, 1966-1967 (Folder 18: 49)
  - Monberg, Helene, 1971 (Folder 18: 50)
  - Monroney, A. S. Mike, 1966 (Folder 18: 51)
  - Montgomery, Fergus, 1967-1994 (Folder 18: 52)
  - Montgomery, W. F., 1961 (Folder 18: 53)
  - Moreell, Ben, 1965 (Folder 18: 54)
  - Morris, Chester, 1961 (Folder 18: 55)
  - Morrison, Toni, 1988 (Folder 18: 56)
  - Morshead, Stuart, 1970-1972 (Folder 18: 57)
  - Moynihan, Daniel, 1975-1978 (Folder 18: 58)
  - Mundt, Karl, 1962 (Folder 18: 59)
  - Murgolo, V. John, 1972 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Napier, John L., 1981-1982 (Folder 19: 2)
  - Nasser, Mahmoud, 1976 (Folder 19: 3)
  - National Alpha Kappa Lambda, 1962 (Folder 19: 4)
  - National Review, 1959-1981 (Folder 19: 5)
  - Nessen, Ron, 1979 (Folder 19: 6)
  - Neuberger, Maurine, 1963 (Folder 19: 7)
  - Neuberger, Richard, 1959 (Folder 19: 8)
  - New American Library, Incorporated (New York), 1967 (Folder 19: 9)
  - New York Herald Tribune, 1963 (Folder 19: 10)
  - New York Times, 1941-1991 (Folder 19: 11)
  - New York Times Book Review, 1962-1969 (Folder 19: 12)
  - News Perspective International, 1970 (Folder 19: 13)
  - Nichols, Lew, 1960 (Folder 19: 14)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1959-1988 (Folder 19: 15)
  - Nofziger, Lyn, 1981 (Folder 19: 16)
  - Novak, Kim, 1968 (Folder 19: 17)
  - Noyes, Newbold, 1972 (Folder 19: 18)
  - Nunn, Sam, 1986 (Folder 19: 19)
  - Oberon, Merle de Pagliai, 1969 (Folder 19: 20)
  - O'Brien, W. E., undated (Folder 19: 21)
  - O'Connor, John J., 1990 (Folder 19: 22)
  - Orell, May, 1966 (Folder 19: 23)
  - Orlando Sentinel, 1971-1972 (Folder 19: 24)
  - Ottenberg, Miriam, undated (Folder 19: 25)